Oluwadare Promise Emmanuel

Game Developer & Blockchain Developer

Address Ife, Osun State Website : Diap.vercel.app

Phone 2349132027991

E-mail Promiseemmanuel.official@gmail.com

Highly proficient Game Developer bringing proven history of successfully utilizing latest technologies to create exciting games. Highly energetic professional with over 4 years of experience and meticulous eye for detail. Thorough understanding of gaming trends combined with expertise in various programming languages.

Knowledgeable professional with a background in Blockchain Development. A driven Fullstack Blockchain Engineer known for reporting on the design process to the appropriate stakeholders and debugging new and existing projects.

Skills

Gaming development
BlockChain Development

Game prototypes

Al Engineer

Work History

2021-09 - Present

Lead Game Developer & Blockchain Developer

Apex Games, United States

 Directing the development team in the design, development, coding, testing and debugging of applications

2021-01 - 2022-03

Game Developer

Lynch games, Germany

- Used debugging techniques to identify issues with computer code and resolve errors.
- Mentored newly hired and junior developers in office and departmental policies and procedures.
- Created prototypes based upon design ideas using such programming languages as C#
- Cultivated professional working relationships with marketing department, other design personnel and upper management.
- Created core game storylines, role-play mechanics and character biographies for new video games franchise.
- Managed project requirements and accomplished objectives by self-monitoring progress and promptly solving issues.

Education

2019-01 - Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science And Engineering

Obafemi Awolowo University - Ife

Software

Unreal Engine

Unity 3D

Blender

ZBrush

Languages

Javascript

Python

C#

C++

Solidity

Rust